<!-- strings.xml are important because it allows the button in a new activity to be reused but
 with a different name. Strings.xml allows to save time and performance -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lim[b]itless</string>
    <string name="capture_image">Take</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="recapture_image">Retake</string>
    <string name="save_image">Save</string>
    <string name="takePicture">Take Picture</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="newSession">New Session</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="galleryButton">Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drawer">Project Lim[b]itless</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>

    <string name="dialog_message">Warning: You will lose all photos from this session</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">Delete Session?</string>
    <string name="ok">Continue</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="guestText">Continue as Guest</string>
    <string name="signInText">Sign In</string>
    <string name="projectLimbitlessTitle">Project Lim(b)itless</string>
    <string name="WelcomeToText">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="string_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="string_next_finish">Next</string>

    <string name="Test_1">testOne</string>
    <string name="Test_2">testTwo</string>
    <string name="Test_3">testThree</string>
    <string name="start_text_welcome_activity">Start</string>
    <string name="ucsd_text_welcome_page">Powered by UC San Diego</string>
    <string name="sign_in_into_your_account_text">Sign into your account</string>
    <string name="new_account_text">New to Lim[b]itless?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_forgot_password">ForgotPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an account</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="reset_password_text"> Please enter your email address. You will receive a link to reset your password shortly.</string>
    <string name="privacy_text">Project Lim(b)itless is a university led research initiative. Types of data collected through the use of this application are user emails, self reported biographical information, and photographic data sent to the cloud based server.
This data is collected to provide essential features for the end user (collecting of limb scans to use for model rendering.) Email and personal information is collected to contact the end user if any issues arise during use of this application.
All of this data is collected voluntarily by filling out the appropriate forms inside of the application and through users sending photographs to the server inside of the gallery function.
Any data collected through this application will not be used for any commercial purposes. This data is intended to be used exclusively for research purposes to increase access to affordable prosthetic limbs.
This privacy policy will be updated directly to new versions of the application during version updates and user consent will be required each time the privacy policy is updated.
All user information is safeguarded internally via protocols that restrict access to relevant researchers. However, the user agrees that they assume any privacy risks of their submitted data.
Questions can be directed to projectlimbitless@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="text_frame_0"> In order to capture a good scan, please find a shaded outdoor area to take photos with minimal glare from the lighting. This process will require an additional person to assist with photo taking. Once a satisfactory location has been found, have the amputee take a seat and assume an appropriate position for imaging. If possible, add a colored-patterned sock on the residual limb. The residual limb should be positioned horizontally, parallel to the ground with sufficient space on all sides for the camera to rotate around.</string>
    <string name="text_frame_1"> In order to obtain accurate measurements from your scan later on, we will need to make 4 markings either directly on the skin of the residual limb or on the sock. For these marks, please place a small, well-known object onto the residual limb. Using a marker that will not smear or fade, please make 4 dots on the top, bottom, right, and left sides of the object. For more information on possible objects to use for scaling, please click here.</string>
    <string name="text_frame_2"> Once everything is set up and the scaling marks are all clearly visible on the skin or sock, you are ready to start the scan. Position the phone at a distance far enough from the residual limb so that its entirety can be seen and no parts are cut off. We recommend starting at the 12 o’clock position as shown in the image above. From there, you may proceed in a clockwise or counterclockwise direction until the 360° rotation is completed. When you are ready, start the session by pressing the capture button and follow the prompts on the screen. Note that during the process of one scan, the capture button only needs to be pressed once.</string>
    <string name="text_frame_3"> While conducting the rotation around the residual limb, please move at a steady and consistent pace. Ensure that the entirety of the limb remains within the green edges at all times. Keep the phone tilted at an angle greater than 10 degrees with the vertical axis, facing the residual limb throughout the entire rotation. Continue to rotate the phone until prompted with the message “Minimum number of photos completed.” At this point, you may choose to terminate the session by pressing stop or continue the session to provide more data by resuming your rotation. Note that sessions stopped prior to the prompt are considered incomplete and do not contain sufficient data.</string>
    <string name="text_frame_4"> When you have completed a scan and saved it into the gallery, make sure to review all photos to ensure that they are evenly lit, in focus, and contain the entire residual limb. From here, you may then choose to name the album and move forward with sending the session to the server. When we receive the information, the development team will reach out to you with further steps.</string>

    <string name="step_1">Step 1: Shade</string>
    <string name="step_2">Step 2: Marks </string>
    <string name="step_3">Step 3: Position</string>
    <string name="step_4">Step 4: Orientation</string>
    <string name="step_5">Step 5: Save and Send</string>
    <string name="about_us">Project Lim(b)itless is an initiative based out of UC San Diego which hopes to increase access to prosthetic
limbs to amputees around the world. Project Lim(b)itless was founded in 2018 as a collaboration between
UC San Diego students in the McKittrick Lab and the Qualcomm Institute. We are very thankful for all of the incredible support we have had on our journey.</string>





</resources>
